<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on menagerie</title>
    <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on menagerie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Argos for NER</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>This semester I am excited to announce that I will be working as a Software Engineer for the Data Visualization and Analysis Team for Notheastern Electric Racing! We are going to be working on a few different really cool projects to help our engineers access and understand data from the car so that they can better improve it.
Currently in development is a project called Argos, essentially a telemetry hub that lets users query any and all data from the car&amp;rsquo;s server, then organizes and presents it in a user-friendly series of charts and figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sherry&#39;s Quizzes</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Sherry&amp;rsquo;s Quizzes is a quiz taking/building web app that I developed, check it out at https://sherrysquizzes-6d15ee4bcb35.herokuapp.com ! Sherry is built in Python with Django as the backend, SQLite database and HTML/CSS as the frontend, hosted on Heroku.
NOTE: I realized on deployment that Django/Heroku is lowkey lame when it comes to serving static files so currently user uploaded images are not displaying until I set up a custom file storage backend w a CDN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Routers, Protocols, Crawlers Oh My!</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 12:42:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-6/</guid>
      <description>In this post we will be looking at two of my favorite projects from a class that I have really been enjoying recently, Networks and Distributed Systems!
The first project we will be looking at is a simplified virtual BGP router. The professors provided us with a simulator and several configs, in which the router we built must be ran against and pass in correctness and performance. Responsibilities of the router included accepting route announcements from simulated peer routers, generating new route announcements for peer routers, managing and compressing forwarding tables, calculating optimal routes, and forwarding data packets that arrive from simulated internet users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCann&#39;s URL Shortener</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-2/</guid>
      <description>McCann&amp;rsquo;s URL Shotener is pretty self-explanatory, Typescript React web app that takes a given long url and shortens it for the user. I built this in a couple days to get experience working with Typesript, React, Express, and testing with Cypress and Jest. I used Chakra UI to use custom fonts, colors, images and other UI stylings.
Locally home page looks like this: 
You can check out the repo at https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning OOD with Java</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-5/</guid>
      <description>So far in my journey with CS at Northeastern, I have completed a few different projects, a couple being interesting enough that I would like to highlight them here and briefly discuss them.
The first project I will be talking about is the Marble Solitaire project. For those that don&amp;rsquo;t know, marble solitaire is a simple board game where you try to hop marbles over each other to eliminate them, the goal is to be left with one marble at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing - Poems</title>
      <link>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leoleader.github.io/menagerie/projects/project-3/</guid>
      <description>These are some of my favorite poems I have written over the years, the first one winning a Scholastic Writing Award which was quite exciting. I like to write in my free time and have dozens of different poems and hope that as time goes on I write many more.
~ Reality ~  ~ Fool&#39;s Love Song ~  ~ The Beast Comes Home ~</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
